Martha Graham Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music Inventory (Box 1-118; 122; 124-197)
  - Choreographed Works (Box 1-191, 193-194)
    - Dello Joio, Norman see Diversion of Angels; A Time of Snow; Triumph of St. Joan [Seraphic Dialogue]
    - Diamond, David see A Formal Dance
    - Dithyrambic, 1931 Composer: Aaron Copland, Copland’s title: Piano Variations.
      - Copyists’ score in ink (incomplete); photocopy laid in (Box-folder 193/11)
    - Diversion of Angels (1948) Composer: Norman Dello Joio, Graham’s title for first performance: Wilderness Stair.
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 58/1)
      - Ink rehearsal piano score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 58/2)
      - Photocopy rehearsal piano score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 58/3)
      - Ozalid wind-piano parts (Box-folder 58/4)
      - Ozalid string parts (Box-folder 58/5)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 58/6)
      - Ozalid extra parts (Box-folder 59/1-6)
    - Drei Klavierstücke, op. 32 see Harlequinade
    - Ecuatorial (1978) Composer: Edgar Varèse
      - Published full score (Box-folder 193/12)
    - Egge, Klaus see Tangled Night
    - El-Dabh, Halim see A Look at Lighting; Lucifer; One More Gaudy Night
    - Elegiac (1933) Composer: Paul Hindemith
      - Copyists’ part for clarinet (Box-folder 193/13)
    - Embattled Garden (1958) Composer: Carlos Surinach
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 62/1)
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 62/2)
      - Piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 62/3)
      - Piano rehearsal score, no choreographic notes (Box-folder 62/4)
      - Piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 62/5)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 63/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 63/4)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 64/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 65/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 66/1-4)
      - Copyist deschens for 3 parts (Box-folder 66/5)
      - Extra copies of copyist deschens for 3 parts (Box-folder 66/6)
    - Engle, Lehman see Transitions
    - Episodes, Part I (1959) Composer: Anton Webern, Webern’s titles: Passacaglia for orchestra, op. 1; Six pieces, op. 6 reconstructed and reworked in 1979.
      - Full score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 67/1)
      - Piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 67/2)
      - Photocopy of piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 67/3)
      - Published parts (Box-folder 67/4-7)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 67/8-10)
      - Published full score, with choreographic notes (Six pieces, op. 6) (Box-folder 68/1)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Six pieces, op. 6) (Box-folder 68/2)
      - Photocopy piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Six pieces, op. 6) (Box-folder 68/3)
      - Published parts (Box-folder 68/4-7)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 68/8-10)
      - Notated piano reduction score: Passacaglia for orchestra, op. 1, photocopy (Box-folder 192/3)
    - Errand into the Maze (1947) Composer: Gian-Carlo Menotti
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 69/1)
      - Ink piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 69/2)
      - Photocopy piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 69/3)
      - Photocopy piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 69/4)
      - Copyist parts, old set (Box-folder 70/1-4)
      - Ozalid old parts (Box-folder 71/1-4)
      - Ozalid old parts (Box-folder 72/1)
      - Deschens, new set of complete parts (Box-folder 72/2)
      - Ozalid woodwind parts, new set (Box-folder 72/3)
      - Ozalid horn-2nd piano (Box-folder 72/4)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 73/1-5)
    - Every Soul is a Circus (1939) Composer: Paul Nordoff
      - Ink conductor’s score (arranged for seven instruments) (Box-folder 75/1)
      - Conductor’s full score (orchestration by Ted Dale) (Box-folder 75/2)
      - Conductor’s full score (arranged for eleven instruments) (Box-folder 75/3)
      - Ink parts (arranged for eleven instruments) (Box-folder 74/1)
      - Piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 74/2)
      - Ink parts (arranged for eleven instruments) (Box-folder 74/3)
      - Ink parts (arranged for seven instruments) (Box-folder 76/1)
      - Ink parts (arranged for twelve instruments) (Box-folder 76/2)
      - Ink piano part (arranged for eleven instruments) (Box-folder 76/3)
      - Parts (arranged by Ted Dale) (Box-folder 77/1)
      - Extra parts, violins (Box-folder 77/2)
      - Extra parts, cello bass, viola (Box-folder 78/1)
      - Negative photostat piano rehearsal score (Box-folder 79/1)
      - Deschens full score (Box-folder 79/2)
      - Negative photostat parts (Box-folder 79/3)
      - Negative photostat piano part (Box-folder 79/4)
      - Negative photostat strings (Box-folder 79/5)
      - Deschens parts (Box-folder 79/6)
    - Eye of Anguish, The (1950) Composer: Vincent Persichetti, Persichetti’s title: Lear.
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 81/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 81/2)
      - Piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 81/3)
      - Piano rehearsal score, without choreographic notes (Box-folder 81/4)
      - Copyist parts (ink) (Box-folder 80/1-3)
    - Fantasy Sonata for Violin and Piano see O Thou Desire to Who Art about to Sing
    - Fine, Vivian see Alcestis
    - Flute of Pan (1978) Composer: [Geheorghe] Zamfir
      - Full score, pencil (Box-folder 193/14)
    - Formal Dance, A (1935) [Later titled Praeludium no. 2] Composer: David Diamond
      - Holograph score and parts (Box-folder 193/15)
      - Flute and clarinet parts (Box-folder 194/8)
    - Frontier (1935) Composer: Louis Horst, Original title of choreography: Perspectives: Frontier and Marching Song.
      - Full score in pencil (Box-folder 82/1)
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 82/2)
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 82/3)
      - Deschens full score (Box-folder 82/4)
      - Piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 82/5)
      - Piano rehearsal score (negative photostat) (Box-folder 82/6)
      - Photocopy piano rehearsal score (Box-folder 82/7)
      - Ink parts (Box-folder 82/8)
      - Ozalid piano part (Box-folder 82/9)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 82/10-11)
      - Ink parts (old set) (Box-folder 82/12)
    - Gershwin, George see But Not For Me
    - Gospel of Eve (1950) Composer: Paul Nordoff
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 83/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 83/2)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 83/3)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, no choreographic notes (Box-folder 83/4)
      - Copyist’s deschen piano rehearsal score (Box-folder 84/1)
      - Copyist’s parts (Box-folder 84/2-3)
    - Green, Ray see American Document
    - Harlequinade (1930) Composer: Ernst Toch, Toch’s title: Drei Klavierstücke, op. 32.
      - Published piano score; photocopy laid in (Box-folder 193/17)
    - Hecabe see Cortege of Eagles
    - Helios, op. 17 see Acts of Light
    - Heloïse and Abelard see Time of Snow
    - Heretic (1929) Composer: Louis Horst, Based on an old Bréton song.
      - Piano fragment in ink (Box-folder 193/18)
      - Piano part (Box-folder 193/19)
      - Photocopy fragment (as recalled by Paul Creston) (Box-folder 193/20)
    - Hérodiade (1944) Composer: Paul Hindemith
      - Photocopy full score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 85/1)
      - Photocopy full score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 85/2)
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 85/3)
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 85/4)
      - Piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (incomplete) (Box-folder 85/5)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 86/1)
      - Extra parts [missing] (Box-folder 86/2)
      - Extra parts, strings (Box-folder 86/3-4)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 87/1-3)
    - Hija de Cólquidea, La see Dark Meadow
    - Hindemith, Paul see Elegiac; Hérodiade
    - Holy Jungle (1974) Composer: Robert Starer
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 88/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 88/2)
      - Piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 88/3)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 88/4-5)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 89/1)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 89/2-4)
    - Horst, Louis see American Document; Celebration; Heretic; Primitive Mysteries; Frontier; El Penitente
    - Hovhaness, Alan see Ardent Song; Circe; Myth of a Voyage
    - Intégrales see Judith
    - Johnson, Hunter see Deaths and Entrances; Letter to the World; Scarlet Letter
    - Judith (1950; new music 1980) Composer, original version: William Schuman
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 194/1)
      - Piano score in ink and pencil, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 194/2)
    - Judith (1980 version) Composer: Edgar Varèse, Varèse’s titles: Intégrales; Offrandes; Octandre.; [Note: In 1934, Graham choreographed a work called Intégrales to music by Varèse.]
      - Published full score Intégrales (Box-folder 90/1)
      - Ozalid full score Intégrales (Box-folder 90/2)
      - Ozalid parts Intégrales (Box-folder 90/3-5)
      - Photocopy full score Offrandes (Box-folder 90/6)
      - Published piano-vocal score Offrandes (Box-folder 91/1)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 91/2-4)
      - Ozalid extra parts (Box-folder 91/5-6)
      - Published full score (part III) Octandre (Box-folder 91/7)
      - Ozalid parts Octandre (Box-folder 91/8-9)
    - Lady of the House of Sleep (1968) Composer: Robert Starer, Earlier title: Hammer of Witches.
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 93/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 93/2)
      - Ozalid rehearsal piano score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 93/3)
      - Ozalid rehearsal piano score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 93/4)
      - Ozalid rehearsal piano score, no choreographic notes (Box-folder 93/5)
      - Deschen parts (Box-folder 92/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 92/4)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 94/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 93/1-3)
    - Lear see Eye of Anguish, The
    - Legend of Judith (1962) Composer: Mordecai Seter
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 96/1)
      - Ozalid full score in 3 volumes (Box-folder 96/2)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 97/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 97/2)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 97/3)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 98/1)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes, 2 volumes (Box-folder 98/2)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes, 2 volumes (Box-folder 98/3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 99/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 100/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 102/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 103/1-2)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 104/1-2)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 105/1-2)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 106/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 107/1-4)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 108/1-4)
    - Lester, Eugene see Archaic Hours, The; Cortege of Eagles; The Plain of Prayer
    - Letter to the World (1940) Composer: Hunter Johnson, Reconstructed in 1988.; Note: Parts are missing.
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 110/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 110/2)
      - Deschens full score (Box-folder 109/1)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 109/2)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 109/3)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, no choreographic notes (Box-folder 109/4)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, no choreographic notes (Box-folder 111/1)
      - Copyist parts (ink) (Box-folder 111/2-4)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 112/1-4)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 113/1-3)
      - Typed script of narration (Box-folder 113/4)
    - Lloyd, Norman see Panorama
    - Look at Lightning, A (1962) Composer: Halim El-Dabh, El-Dabh’s title: Mekta’ In the Art of Kita’.
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 117/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 117/2)
      - Published piano score (Box-folder 117/3)
      - Published piano score with choreographic notes (Box-folder 117/4)
      - Published piano score with choreographic notes (Box-folder 117/5)
      - Holograph in pencil (Box-folder 117/6)
      - Ozalid parts, flute-harp (Box-folder 117/7)
      - Extra parts [some missing] (Box-folder 117/8-9)
    - Lucifer (1975) Composer: Halim El-Dabh
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 194/3)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 194/4)
    - Lux Aterna for 5 Masked Musicians see Phaedra’s Dream
    - Medea see Cave of the Heart
    - Mekta’ In the Art of Kita’ see Look at Lightning, A
    - Menotti, Gian-Carlo see Errand into the Maze
    - Momenta Rustica (1929) Composer: Françoise Poulenc
      - Published piano four hands (incomplete) (Box-folder 194/5)
    - Morisca see Serenata Morisca
    - Music for Martha Graham see Ardent Song
    - Myth of a Voyage (1973) Composer: Alan Hovhaness
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 114/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 114/2)
      - Ozalid full score (original version) (Box-folder 114/3)
      - Ozalid full score (original version) (Box-folder 114/4)
      - Copyist full score (Box-folder 114/5)
      - Photocopy piano rehearsal score (incomplete) (Box-folder 115/1)
      - Copyist Deschens (Box-folder 115/2)
      - Copyist Deschens (Box-folder 115/3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 115/4)
      - Original parts (Box-folder 115/5)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 116/1-4)
    - Nielson, Carl see Acts of Light
    - New Dance see Steps in the Street
    - Night Journey (1947) Composer: William Schuman
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 118/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 118/2)
      - Ink piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 118/3)
      - Negative Photostat piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 118/4)
      - Ozalid parts, old set (Box-folder 118/5-6)
      - Deschens parts, new set (Box-folder 122/1)
      - Ozalid extra parts, new set (Box-folder 122/2-4)
    - Nocturne for Orchestra see Dances of the Golden Hall
    - Nordoff Paul see Every Soul is a Circus; Gospel of Eve; Salem Shore
    - Octandre see Judith
    - Offrandes see Judith
    - One More Gaudy Night (1961) Composer: Halim El-Dabh
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 125/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 125/2)
      - Ozalid piano score (Box-folder 126/1)
      - Ozalid piano score (Box-folder 126/2)
      - Ozalid piano score (Box-folder 126/3)
      - Ozalid parts, woodwinds (Box-folder 126/4)
      - Ozalid parts, brass-harp (Box-folder 127/1)
      - Ozalid parts, string (Box-folder 127/2)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 127/3-5)
    - Opening Dance for Martha Graham see Panorama
    - Ornstein Leo see Poems of 1917
    - O Thou Desire to Who Art about to Sing (1977) Composer: Meyer Kupferman, Kupferman’s title: Fantasy Sonata for Violin and Piano.
      - Published score and part (Box-folder 124/1)
      - Published score and part (Box-folder 124/2)
      - Photocopy score “Death and Water” (Box-folder 124/3)
      - Photocopy score “Suspended Sun Solo” (Box-folder 124/4)
      - Photocopy score “Stars Duet” (Box-folder 124/5)
      - Photocopy score “Wind” (Box-folder 124/6)
      - Photocopy score “Fire” (Box-folder 124/7)
      - Photocopy score “Sun and Moon Love Duet” (Box-folder 124/8)
    - Owl and the Pussycat (1978) Composer: Carlos Surinach
      - Ozalid full score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 128/1)
      - Ozalid full score, no choreographic notes (Box-folder 128/2)
      - Ozalid full score, no choreographic notes (Box-folder 128/3)
      - Photocopy, full score, no choreographic notes (Box-folder 128/4)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 129/1)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 129/2-5)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 129/6-7)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 130/1-4)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 131/1-4)
      - Ozalid full score, reduced orchestra (Box-folder 132/1)
      - Ozalid parts, reduced orchestra (Box-folder 132/2-4)
      - Extra parts, reduced orchestra (Box-folder 132/5)
    - Panorama (1935) Composer: Norman Lloyd
      - Reduction, arranged by Stanley Sussman (Box-folder 133/1)
      - Photocopy reduction, arranged by Stanley Sussman (Box-folder 133/2)
      - Photocopy piano score (Box-folder 133/3)
      - Photocopy piano score (Box-folder 133/4)
      - Copyist’s ink deschens, parts (Sussman arrangement) (Box-folder 134/1)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 134/2-6)
      - Ink piano score, Opening Dance for Martha Graham (Box-folder 194/6)
    - Pan og Syrinx [Pan and Syrinx], op. 49 see Acts of Light
    - Panufnik, Andrzei see Dances of the Golden Hall
    - Part Real-Part Dream (1965) Composer: Mordecai Seter, Seter’s title: Concertante.
      - Conductor’s score (Box-folder 139/1)
      - Piano-rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 135/1)
      - Conductor’s score (Box-folder 135/2)
      - Conductor’s score, no. 2 (Box-folder 135/3)
      - String parts (Box-folder 136/1)
      - Parts (woodwinds, brass, harp, celeste); Deschen parts for flute (Box-folder 137/1)
      - Ink deschens, full score (Box-folder 138/1)
      - Ink deschens, copyist parts, woodwinds and brass (Box-folder 138/2)
      - Ink deschens, copyist parts, percussion-harp (Box-folder 138/3)
      - Ink deschens, copyist parts, strings (Box-folder 138/4)
      - Miscellaneous inserts (Box-folder 138/5)
    - Passacaglia for Orchestra, op. 1 see Episodes: Part I
    - Penitente, El (1940) Composer: Louis Horst
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 61/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 61/2)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 61/3)
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 61/4)
      - Ink piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 60/1)
      - Ozalid piano part (Box-folder 60/2)
      - Ozalid piano part (Box-folder 60/3)
      - Ozalid piano part (Box-folder 60/4)
      - Photocopy set of parts (Box-folder 60/5)
      - Photocopy extra parts (Box-folder 60/6-7)
    - Persichetti, Vincent see Eye of Anguish, The
    - Perspectives: Frontier and Marching Song see Frontier
    - Phaedra (1962) Composer: Robert Starer
      - Full score (Box-folder 140/1)
      - Full score (arrarnge for seven instruments) (Box-folder 140/2)
      - Ink full score (Box-folder 140/3)
      - Piano-rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 141/1)
      - Piano-rehearsal score, without choreographic notes (Box-folder 141/2)
      - Piano-rehearsal score, incomplete (Box-folder 141/3)
      - Parts (flute, clarinet, English horn, bassoon, horn, percussion [4], piano, oboe, trumpet, trombone) (Box-folder 142/1)
      - String parts (violin I, violin II, viola, cello, bass) (Box-folder 143/1)
      - Full set of parts (Box-folder 144/1)
      - “Tiento de Peña,” violin (ink) part (Box-folder 146/1)
      - “Phaedra” Ozalid, violin I part (Box-folder 146/2)
      - Deschens string parts (Box-folder 146/3-7)
    - Phaedra’s Dream (1983) Composer: George Crumb, Crumb’s title: Lux Aterna for 5 Masked Musicians.
      - Published full score (Box-folder 145/1)
      - Parts (Box-folder 145/2)
    - Piano Concerto no. 2, op. 21 see Tangled Night
    - Piano Variations see Dithyrambic
    - Plain of Prayer, The (1968) Composer: Eugene Lester
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 148/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 148/2)
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 148/3)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 148/4)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, no choreographic notes (Box-folder 148/5)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 147/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 149/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 150/1-4)
    - Poems of 1917 (1928) Composer: Leo Ornstein
      - Published piano score (Box-folder 194/7)
    - Point of Crossing (1975) Composer: Mordecai Seter
      - Published extra parts (Box-folder 151/1-5)
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 152/1)
      - Published full score (Box-folder 152/2)
      - Published parts (Box-folder 152/3-6)
      - Published extra parts (Box-folder 152/7-8)
    - Poulanc, Françoise see Momenta Rustica
    - Praeludium no. 2 see A Formal Dance
    - Prelude to Action(from Chronicle) (1936) Composer: Wallingford Riegger, Arrangement, orchestration, and additional music by Stanley Sussman.
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 153/1)
      - Photocopied parts (Box-folder 153/2-5)
      - Photocopied extra parts (Box-folder 154/1-5)
    - Primitive Mysteries (1931) Composer: Louis Horst
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 155/1)
      - Oboe part (Box-folder 155/2)
      - Flute part (Box-folder 155/3)
      - Ozalid piano part (Box-folder 155/4)
      - Ink piano score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 155/5)
      - Ozalid piano score (Box-folder 155/6)
      - Ozalid piano score (Box-folder 155/7)
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 155/8)
    - Punch and the Judy (1941) Composer: Robert McBride
      - Ink piano score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 156/1)
      - Photocopy piano score, no choreographic notes (Box-folder 156/2)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 156/3)
      - Ozalid 2-piano version (Box-folder 157/1)
      - Ozalid 2-piano version (Box-folder 157/2)
      - Copyist’s parts, woodwinds (Box-folder 157/3)
      - Copyist’s parts in ink, bassoon, horn, piano (Box-folder 158/1)
      - Copyist’s parts in ink, violin I and violin II (Box-folder 158/2)
      - Copyist’s parts in ink, viola, violoncello, double bass (Box-folder 158/3)
      - Ozalid parts, alternate version (Box-folder 158/4-6)
    - Riegger, Wallingford see Baccanale; Prelude to Action; Steps in the Street
    - Ribbink, Thomas see Canticle for Innocent Comedians
    - Rite of Spring (1984) Composer: Igor Stravinsky
      - Published score, revised version with reduced orchestra by Robert Rudolf (Box-folder 159/1)
      - Published score, revised version with reduced orchestra by Robert Rudolf (Box-folder 159/2)
      - Photocopy published score, revised version with reduced orchestra by Robert Rudolf (Box-folder 159/3)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 160/1-4)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 161/1-5)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 162/104)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 163/1-4)
    - Salem Shore (1943) Composer: Paul Nordoff
      - Ozalid rehearsal piano score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 164/1)
      - Ink full score reduction, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 164/2)
      - Photocopy of full score reduction, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 164/3)
      - Set of parts for 4 instruments (Box-folder 164/4)
      - Ozalid full score for 7 instruments (Box-folder 164/5)
      - Photocopy full score, with pencil emendations (Box-folder 165/1)
      - Copyist’s deschens parts (Box-folder 166/2)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 166/3-6)
    - Satyric Festival Song (1932) Composer: Arma, Paul [Imre Weisshaus]
      - Ink piccolo part, Satyric Festival Song (Box-folder 194/9)
    - Scarlet Letter, The (1975) Composer: Hunter Johnson
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 166/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 166/2)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 167/1)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 167/2-4)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 168/1)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 168/2-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 169/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 170/1-3)
    - Satie, Erik see Trois Gnossiennes
    - Schuman, William see Judith; Night Journey; Voyage; Witch of Endor
    - Secular Games (1962) Composer: Robert Starer, Starer’s title: Concerto a tre.
      - Published score and parts (Box-folder 194/11)
    - Seraphic Dialogue see Triumph of St. Joan
    - Serenata, op. 13 see Serenata Morisca